{
    "subject": "resource/Lane_College",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:National_Register_of_Historic_Places_in_Tennessee",
    "human_readable": "Lane College is about National Register of Historic Places in Tennessee.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8914793133735657,
            "question": "In which state is Lane College listed on the National Register of Historic Places?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.855670690536499,
            "question": "Are there any other notable historical sites in Tennessee besides Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7341704368591309,
            "question": "Does being listed on the National Register of Historic Places offer any benefits to Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7145535349845886,
            "question": "Where is Lane College located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.57569819688797,
            "question": "What is the National Register of Historic Places?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5234406590461731,
            "question": "Why might a college be listed on the National Register of Historic Places?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49060365557670593,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Lane College's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3478149473667145,
            "question": "What significant designation does Lane College hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31018173694610596,
            "question": "What are some examples of other types of places listed on the National Register of Historic Places?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06184867396950722,
            "question": "What is the significance of historic preservation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lane College is about National Register of Historic Places in Tennessee.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4046_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of other types of places listed on the National Register of Historic Places?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4046_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant designation does Lane College hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4046_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can we learn more about Lane College's history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4046_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4046_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Lane College is associated with the National Register of Historic Places in Tennessee. Specifically, the document mentions that \"The campus is listed on National Register of Historic Places as the Lane College Historic District (NRHP District No. 87001117).\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}